欢迎回来 长官
Welcome back, sir.
你们做了什么？
What have you done?
为了挽救您的生命所必须做的 塞拉斯
What we needed to in order to save you, Silas.
我…成他们中的一员了！
I'm one of them.
借助生物科技实验的终极研究成果
The logical evolution of MECH's experiments and biotech.
您的大脑与捐赠者的神经和骨骼系统连接在了一起
Your brain fused with the donor's nervous and skeletal systems.
人类与机器的完美结合 如此精湛…
The perfect meld of man and machine. Exquisite.
感谢你们这一生为我所做的贡献
Thank you all for your dedication and a lifetime of service.
不过 我现在觉得自己更适合与那群巨人为伍了
But I now seem more suited to keep the exclusive company of titans.
我是莱兰・毕晓普上校
Colonel Leland Bishop.
隔板 你真的不能让自己这么衰弱下去
Bulkhead, you really mustn't allow yourself to decline.
对啊 小隔 你应该从沮丧中走出来！
Yeah, Bulk. You got to pull yourself out of this funk.
有什么用？
What's the use?
你真的需要加强体能
You need to regain your strength.
只要假以时日 你就能…
The time will come when...
能怎么样？帮上你们大家的忙？
When what? When all of you will need an assist?
那要新来的家伙干嘛？
Isn't that what the new guy's for?
嘿 隔板 我一直在想 考虑到你的伤势
Hey, Bulkhead, I've been thinking. With your injury and all
你不妨试试我从红蜘蛛那儿弄来的盔甲
you might want to take advantage of the armor I snagged from Starscream.
即穿即用的肌肉外套！
Instant muscle suit!
你认为我得去拄拐？
You think I need a crutch?!
隔板！那个我还有用呐！
Bulkhead, I needed that!
别挡道 新兵蛋子！
Out of my way, rookie!
他能走路了！
He can walk!
要我说 他完全可以执行任务了！
Looks like he's fit for duty to me.
你甚至都不知道自己在说什么
You don't even know what you're talking about.
你不是开玩笑吧 拉夫！
You've got to be kidding, Raf.
你这种模范学生 被禁足了？
You of all people grounded?
闹大了！我漏掉了一些作业 还搞砸了几门考试
Big time. I misplaced some homework and blew a couple of tests.
搞砸了是指：成绩从“A”变成了“A-”
Translation: "A-" instead of "A."
可能我耗在基地的时间过多了吧
I'm probably spending too much time at the base.
拉斐尔 我希望你没在那儿打电话
Rafael, I hope you're not on the phone in there.
没 妈妈 帮我跟小蜂打个招呼
No, mama! Say hello to Bee for me.
还有 在我的成绩提高之前 我没法呆在领袖卫队了
By time I improve these grades, I'm off team Prime.
好容易回来一个 立马又走了一个
Just when we get one back, we lose another.
奇怪啊
Strange.
威震天陛下 看起来打击的生命信号又出现了
Lord Megatron, it appears that Breakdown's signal has popped back online
尽管受到了污染
all be it corrupted.
谨慎前往调查 这很可能是汽车人的陷阱
Investigate with caution. It may well be an Autobot trick.
这是当然
I certainly hope not.
打击表面上是一只猛兽 但在旋转缓冲器下隐藏着一颗艺术家的心
Breakdown may act a brute, but he's a maestro behind a rotary buffer.
打击！这些日子你上…
Breakdown, where have you...
打击？谁欺负你了？
Breakdown, what happened to you?
这说来话长 而且威震天对这个一定更感兴趣！
There lies a tale which won't be nearly as interesting to Megatron as this.
所以 带我去见你的头目吧
So, take me to your leader.
下午4点30分时 一颗卫星从高安全等级的军需库中被盗
At 16:30 hours, a satellite was stolen from a high-security military bolt.
监控录像显示那个名叫打击的霸天虎离开过现场
Surveillance shows the Decepticon known as Breakdown at the scene.
有阵子没见过他了
Haven't seen him in a while.
似乎在打击以汽车形态进入基地的时候
It looks like Breakdown entered the base in vehicle mode
车上还有个人
with someone behind the wheel.
一个霸天虎和一个人类成双入对？
A Decepticon paired with a human?
此外我基本上猜出那人是谁了
And I have a pretty good hunch who.
被偷的卫星原属于达摩克利斯计划
The stolen satellite was project Damocles.
塞拉斯发明的东西
Invented by Silas.
我猜是前上校毕晓普想翻旧帐了
I guess the former Colonel Bishop wanted it back.
是啊 我还以为塞拉斯已经成过去式了！
Yeah, I thought Silas was paste!
包括我在内！
So did I.
福勒探员 就算他还活着
Agent Fowler, even if he were alive
你认为他能和霸天虎勾结在一起么？
are you suggesting that Silas has allied MECH with the Decepticons?
我极度怀疑威震天会考虑这个主意！
I highly doubt that Megatron would entertain such an idea.
为什么不呢？我们人机合作得就很不错嘛！
Why not? The human-bot alliance works for us.
大多数时候吧…
Most of the time.
击倒 这个令人作呕的东西是什么？
Knockout, what is this abomination?!
你竟然还把它带到这儿来？
And why have you brought it here?
我是塞拉斯 全称“增强型人机共存生命体”
I am Silas, as in cybernetic life augmented by symbiosis.
我来是有个提议
I come with a proposition.
这就是那个把打击解剖的人类！
This is the human who dissected Breakdown.
我的君王 请您允许我以牙还牙
Please, my liege, allow me to return the favor.
我建议您不要忽略一个让擎天柱占尽上风的资产 至少在这个星球上
I propose that you not overlook the one asset that provides Optimus Prime an advantage... at least, on this world.
你是指…
And that would be?
人类因素
The human factor.
看看你的周围吧 塞拉斯！
Look around you, Silas!
我统领着一支来自强大战舰上的军队
I command an army from a mighty warship.
相较之下 一个渺小的人类能为我提供什么？！
What could a human possibly offer?
我可不是普通的人类 这也并非普通的武器
I am no ordinary human, and this is no ordinary weapon.
达摩克利斯是一门粒子炮 它的力量足以把五角大楼像生日蛋糕一样切开
Damocles is a particle-beam cannon so powerful it can slice up the Pentagon like a birthday cake
从卫星轨道上用那东西 我能把拉什莫尔山的人都剃成莫霍克头
or give everyone on Mount Rushmore a mohawk, all from a satellite in orbit.
这是一个疯子的发明 还落在了威震天手里
It's the work of a madman. And in Megatron's hands...
一把利剑 高悬在这星球上每个人的头顶？
A threat to anyone, anywhere on the planet.
只需轻轻碰一下开关
With pinpoint accuracy at the flick of a switch.
那么你想要什么回报？
And what is it that you... wish in return?
只要能在您这里获得一席之地…
Merely a place at the table.
虎子们或许能夺取卫星 但没有接入密码就无法控制它
The Cons may have the satellite, but they can't use it without the interface code.
唯一的副本被保存在卡罗拉多州总部的安全服务器上
The only existing copy is stored on the secured servers at headquarters in Colorado.
我们必须不惜一切代价阻止霸天虎获得密码
We must keep the code out of Decepticon hands at all costs.
表演时间到了！
It's roll time.
那个…我还没说你能执行任务呢 更别说你现在根本没做好准备！
Ep, ep... ! I have not yet cleared you for active duty, nor are you ready to roll.
注意！所有人员紧急疏散
Attention, all personnel are ordered to evacuate immediately.
这里发生5级生化辐射泄露 重复 立即疏散！
We have a level 5 radiation leak. Repeat, evacuate immediately.
霸天虎捷足先登了！我们必须保护指挥中心！
The Decepticons have proceeded us. We must secure the command center.
汽车人也到了！
The Autobots have arrived.
威震天 放轻松！
Megatron, relax.
威震天…陛下
Lord Megatron.
声波或许需要下载密码 才能让您在战舰里直接遥控达摩克利斯
Soundwave may need to download the code in order to remotely operated Damocles from here on your warship
不过一旦侵入了中央处理器 他就能任意控制达摩克利斯了！
but while jacked into the mainframe, Damocles is his to command.
声波 准备进行测试！
Soundwave, prepare to beta test.
大有搞头啊…
Promising.
撤退！
Fall back!
救护车 请求支援！
Ratchet, we require backup.
马上就到！
- I'm there.\N- You can't yet!
你能按福勒探员的意见来远程关闭达摩克利斯吗？
Can you remotely disable project Damocles under Agent Fowler's advisement?
用人类的电脑网络？
On a human-based computer network
在缺少助手…缺少拉斐尔的情况下？
without my backup? Without Rafael?
你们干嘛来这儿？
Wha... what are you guys doing here?
孩子 地球母亲需要你
Son, your planet needs you.
汽车人 我们必须把它的注意力从拉斐尔那里引开
Autobots, we must draw its fire to distract from Rafael's efforts.
我倒觉得这完全不是问题
Somehow I don't think that'll be a problem.
救护车 你必须送我过去！
Ratchet, you've got to send me in.
好让你当个移动标靶？
So you can be an even easier target?
你现在连行动都不能自理
You have yet to regain your full range of motion!
可是打击回来了 他可是我的老冤家
But Breakdown's back. He's my archenemy.
拜托 连孩子们都在忙乎呢！
Come on, even the kids are in on the action!
好吧 隔板 你现在可以去执行任务了
Very well, Bulkhead. You are cleared for duty.
太好了！
Yes!
是我给你的任务！
A duty of my choosing.
我黑进去了 但我没法接触目标系统 防火墙太多了
I'm in, but I can't reach the targeting systems. Too many firewalls.
加油 孩子！要是虎子带着密码逃了
Come on, son. If the Cons make off with that interface code
达摩克利斯可就能全天候在天上开火了！
Damocles will light up the sky 24-7.
就让他们带走密码好了 反正那也没法帮他们使用卫星
Let them have the code. It won't do them any good without the satellite.
我没听明白
Can't say I follow you.
任何卫星都会有推进器 这是他们用来调整轨道的
All satellites have maneuvering thrusters so they can adjust their orbits.
如果我能黑进航行子程序 就能彻底关掉卫星
If I can break into the navigation subroutine, I can bring the whole satellite down.
好极了！顺便 呃…洗手间在哪儿？
Great. Say, um... which way is the bathroom?
什么？不！要是我妈妈看见你…
What? No! If my Mom sees you...
甭担心 叔叔可是在隐蔽行动中练过的
Relax. I trained in covert ops.
你就是被忍者训练过我也不管 我妈的眼睛无处不在
I don't care if you were trained by a ninja. My Mom has eyes in the back of your head!
有人入侵了系统？声波 我们有漏洞了！
An intruder in the system? Soundwave, we have a breach!
贾斯帕 内华达 那只可能是汽车人的人类同盟
Jasper, Nevada. It can only be the Autobots' human allies.
或许你可以把这件事处理一下！
Then perhaps you should attend to the matter.
显然您的部下更适合执行这个任务
Surely one of your subordinates is more suitable.
快去！
Now!
畅通无阻 我要上了！
Clear shot! I'm going in!
还是再议吧！
Scratch that.
晚上好 黑客
Good night, hacker.
我喜欢这支线任务 老救！
Good call on curbside duty, Ratch.
我想你想的拳头发痒 你跑哪儿去了 打击？
Been itching to trade pay with you again. Where you been, Breakdown?
别着急 我马上就送你去那边见他
Be patient. I'm about to send you there.
你不是打击？
You're not Breakdown.
但你是隔板 这是你最后一次干扰我的行动了
But you are Bulkhead, and this is the last time you'll interfere with one of my operations.
塞拉斯？
Silas?
在肉体上…从某种意义上来说
In the flesh, in a manner of speaking.
隔板你听到了吗？隔板！
Bulkhead, do you read? Bulkhead!
擎天柱 恐怕隔板需要紧急支援！
Optimus, I fear that Bulkhead requires immediate backup.
可恶 他们都把参数藏在哪儿了？
Oh, where did they hide the substringing?
我说 你家卫生纸不多了
FYI, you're low on T.P.
反应太慢了 你太依赖右拳了
Reaction time is slow. You're favoring your right side.
步法太乱
Legs are weak.
让你见识一下什么叫乱！
I'll show you weak.
你该躺在病床上的 汽车人
You should have stayed in bed, Autobot.
我来支援 这是新人该干的！
Assist... what the new guy's for.
听我这个老“新人”一言…
One new guy to another...
今天是你最后一次打卡了！
This is your final day on the job.
他们的意图是关闭卫星！
They're attempting to disable the satellite!
塞拉斯 砸扁一个人类小孩对你来说就那么难吗！
Silas, how difficult is it to squash a human child?!
塞拉斯！
Silas!
我们有密码了 直接瞄准黑客 消灭他！
We have the codes? Then target the intruder and destroy him!
我们的机会来了 汽车人 向指挥中心进攻！
This is our opportunity. Autobots, storm the command center.
就要成功了
I'm almost there.
干得好 拉夫！它动起来了！
Raf, rock on! It's moving.
呃 那不是我干的…
Uh, that isn't me.
啊 伙计们？那是贾斯帕
Uh, guys... that's Jasper.
哇唔 我能看到我监护人的房子！
Ooh, I can see my host parents' house.
而我能看到我家 就在目标范围内！
And I can see my house right in their target sights.
他们随时会开火 孩子！
Any time, son.
全力推进！
Full thruster burn.
你…你真是个天才！
Yes! You're a genius!
拉斐尔…？怎么这么吵 你到底在干什么？
Rafael. Jorge Gonzales Esquivel! What is going on in here?
学习研讨会！
Study group.
塞拉斯 立即返回基地！
Silas, return to base immediately.
看来某人的宏伟计划又一次泡了汤！
Looks like someone's big plan just burned up in re-entry.
说到雷霆救援队 我研究过你们的每一场战斗
And for the record, I studied every one of the Wrecker's battles.
你还是有希望入队的 新兵蛋子！
There's hope for you yet, newbie.
塞拉斯 你已经赢得了你的席位
Silas, you have earned your place at the table.
威震天陛下 这是我的荣幸
Lord Megatron, I am honored.
在击倒的解剖台上！
Knockout's dissection table.
打击会为此泉下有知的
Breakdown would be tickled.
不 威震天陛下 为什么？
No, lord Megatron. Why?
因为达摩克利斯是你所能提供的最好的东西
Because Damocles was the best you had to offer
而它现在已经没了 人类因素的确起到了决定性作用
and it is no more. The human factor did indeed tip the scales...
而获益者是我的敌人！
in favor of my enemies.
他会是个迷人的研究素材…
He will be a fascinating case for study.
我会好好研究他 一片纤维都不会落下…
I will leave no fiber or fiber optic unexamined.
不 不 威震天 我是来为您效忠的！
No, no. Megatron, I'm here to serve you!
不 不 不！！！
No! No! Nooo!